Armageddon
Shoot
Imma get ’em
Watch Uh
Imma bite back Uh
짙은 어둠이
막아설 땐 Uh
한 걸음 앞으로
날아든 It’s bad
사라진 Feedback
시작된 Code black Uh
깊어가
혼란스러운 밤
악몽은 또 짙게 번져가
뭔갈 숨기려고 해
I got it, I got it
혼돈을 타고
덮쳐 Killing like
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
’Cause I wanna see
I wanna see truly
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
내게 다가와 다가와
Imma get it
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get ’em
Shoot
Hey Ya
또 다른 나
우릴 막지 마
We never play nice
Shoot
완벽한 Pair
넌 똑같은 Soul
Three to get ready
우린 Shoot and go
겁 없이 누벼
날 이끄는 Way
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
Yes I’m gonna see
I’m gonna see, want it
Bang chitty bang
Bang chitty bang bang
답이 들려와 들려와
Imma get it
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Imma get ’em
또 어둠을 몰아내고
시작을 꽃피운 너와 나의 Story
더 완벽해진 우리
(Armageddon)
정의해 이젠
나만의 Complete
내 모든 걸 이끌어
Do it all myself
완전한 나를 이뤄내
(Drop)
Throw it back,
throw it back,
throw it back
Born like a queen
Born like a king Ya
Throw it back,
throw it back,
throw it back
불러
Imma get ’em
Done
(Aw wayo wayo)
널 향해 겨눠 Get it, gone
이젠 널 끝내 Better run
(끝을 모르는 너와 나 You gonna, gonna)
깨트려 거침없이 Done
(Go way up, way up)
Full shot pull it up Armageddon
Armageddon
(Aw wayo wayo wayo Warning all night long)
(Aw wayo wayo)
끝과 시작의
Armageddon